What?!
He’s the Godfather?
Governor, don’t listen to her!
He’s a fraud!
The guards are here to arrest him,
and they’re still putting on this act!
You do remember you came here to
congratulate the Godfather, right?
So what?
Do you really think the real Godfather
would grovel and flatter someone like you?
What the hell is going on here?
Who is the real Godfather?
Maybe this will jog your memory.
You… you’re Lady Cassia, the Judgment Knight?
You begged repeatedly for an invitation to the Godfather’s wedding.
To keep his identity hidden,
I specifically told you to address him as "Mr. Carter".
Remember?
Yes… yes, of course.
Now tell me.
Who do you think the real Godfather is?
Godfather!
Finally, someone with a brain.
Get up.
Thank you, Godfather!
This man called me a fraud and tried to arrest me.
Governor, what do you think should be done with him?
What?!
He dared try to arrest the Godfather?
Strip him of his rank and throw him in the death cells!
Governor, please!
I was only following orders!
I didn’t know anything!
It was him!
He’s the one who said it!
You bastard!
You dared slander the Godfather?
No, Governor!
He’s the impostor!
No one here believes her!